(Raj:)Then you have nothing
to worry about.
(Leonard:)No, I do not.
(Leonard:)You are a mean little man.
(Raj:)You'd think it'd be because
my parents didn't love me,
(Raj:)but actually they
loved me a great deal.
(Howard:)Bernie, it's not you.
(Howard:)She's just set
in her ways.
(Bernadette:)How can we be together
if the thought of us
(Leonard:)getting married
might kill your mother?
(Howard:)It's the circle
of life, sweetie.
(Howard:)One day our son will marry
someone and it will kill you.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I have to go
to the bathroom
(Sheldon:)and no one
will take me home.
(Howard:)What's wrong with
the bathroom here?
(Sheldon:)Pneumococcus, streptococcus,
staphylococcus
(Sheldon:)and other assorted
coccuses.
(Howard:)Sheldon, my mother is
on her deathbed
and my fiancée is grief-stricken
over putting her there.
(Howard:)I'm not taking you home.
(Sheldon:)Will you at least
(Sheldon:)go with me to the restroom here,
(Sheldon:)so you can open the door
and flush the urinal?